发射倒数60秒[太空倒数用语]
T minus 60 seconds
终于到了这关键一刻
Oh, it all comes down to this!
我紧张到胃酸要逆流成河了
Oh, I've got butterflies.
别在这时候掉链子  霍夫斯塔德
Don't get soft on me, Hofstadter.
小心爷一掌把你脸上的眼镜都打飞
I will slap those glasses right off your face.
你们这是干嘛
What's going on?
我们要抢动漫展的票
Hey. We're about to buy tickets for Comic-Con.
发射倒数45秒
T Minus 45 seconds!
票总是被秒速抢光
They sell out incredibly fast,
但只要一人挤进  大家就都能...
but as long as one of us gets in, we can buy passes...
我的天啊  现在不是调情的时候
Good Lord, this is not the time for flirting!
别淫虫上脑了好吗
Keep it in your pants!
喝上咖啡前就有这种怪事
It's a whole lot of weird before coffee.
发射倒数30秒
T-minus 30 seconds!
我真的忍不住要去嘘嘘了
Oh, I have to go to the bathroom so bad.
每年我都叫你穿上尿布
Every year! I told you, wear a diaper!
我也早说了我会起尿布疹
And I told you I get diaper rash!
15秒
15 seconds!
关键时刻来了
Oh, this is it!
成败就此一举
This is it!
要来啦
This is it.
倒数5  4  3
Five, four, three,
-2  1  -开卖啦
- two, one. - It's live.
快点  快点  快点
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
有人挤进了吗
Anyone in?!
-没  -还没
- No! - Not yet!
记得一直按F5刷新页面
Do not stop refreshing your screens!
-刷  -刷
- Refresh. - Refresh.
我刷
Refresh.
我刷  我再刷
Refresh. Refresh.
我刷  我刷  我刷刷
Refresh. Refresh. Refresh...
要忍这帮怪人  这么小杯咖啡一定不够啊
Yeah, this is not gonna be enough coffee.
我刷  我刷  我刷刷
Refresh. Refresh. Refresh.
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
生活大爆炸
第七季  第十四集
我刷  我刷  我刷刷
Refresh... Refresh... Refresh...
我刷  我再刷
Refresh... Refresh...
Refresh. Refresh.
刷刷刷
Refresh.
我刷  都过了十分钟了
Refresh. It's been ten minutes!
快没时间了
We're running out of time.
耍帅时间吗  是啊
To be cool? Yeah.
我成功了  我挤进买票队伍里了
I did it! I did it! I'm in the queue!
消防员算啥英雄  他才是真英雄
And they say firefighters are the real heroes.
你购票序号是第几
Uh, what number in line are you?
-第15  -太好了
- Uh, 15... - Great!
-第15211个  -我靠
- ...thousand, 211. - Damn!
只剩下周四跟周日的票了
Oh, they only have Thursday and Sunday passes left.
-是吗  -现在周四也没了  只剩周日的了
- Really? - Oh, Thursday's gone. Just Sunday left.
周日是最差劲的一天了  都没什么人了
Oh, Sunday's the worst. Everybody's leaving,
大部分值得看的访谈也都结束了
most of good panels are over,
剩下的主题T恤也只剩小号跟超超超超大号
the only T-shirts left are small and XXXXL
周日的票也没了
Sunday's gone.
别啊  我超爱周日的
Not Sunday! I love Sunday!
所以就这样  票全都卖完了吗
So that's it? Everything's sold out?
是的
Yeah.
真不敢相信我们去不成了
I can't believe we're not going.
没事的
It's okay.
阿纳海姆市也有另一个动漫展啊
You know, there-there's always WonderCon in Anaheim.
那个展也还行啊
That-That's just as good.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
你们真是太可怜了
Oh, guys, this is really sad.
而且是有别于20分钟前的那种可怜
And in a different way than it was 20 minutes ago.
我们浪费大把时间制作绿巨人服装  现在全打水漂了
I can't believe we wasted all that time on our Hulk costumes.
你们本来全打算打扮成绿巨人啊
You were all going as the Hulk?
不是同一版的绿巨人
Not the same Hulk.
77年版  03年版  08年版  复联版
Ferrigno, Bana, Norton and Ruffalo.
本来我们会是化装舞会上的一群
We would have been the angry green belles
愤怒绿色佳人呢
of the masquerade ball.
是啊
Yeah.
现在又变回第一种"可怜"了
And we're back to the first kind of sad.
先生们  我有方法解决动漫展问题了
Gentlemen, I have the solution to our Comic-Con problem.
忘了那个破展吧
We don't need them.
我要自己办一个动漫展
I'm starting my own convention.
谢尔顿  就跟我们一起去买黄牛票嘛
Sheldon, just buy scalped tickets with us.
我告诉你  买黄牛票是违反大会规定的
I told you. Buying scalped tickets is against the rules.
如被发现  终身不得再参与动漫展
If you get caught, you get banned from Comic-Con for life.
终身啊  莱纳德
Life, Leonard.
想想等我们80岁  你载我去参加动漫展
You're gonna feel pretty silly when we're 80 years old,
可你进不去  得在车上等我三天时
and you have to drive me down there
你就会懊恼自己现在的决定
and then wait in the car for three days.
随便你
Do what you want.
我们要去买黄牛票
We're getting scalped tickets.
我已经在网上找到一个愿意卖的人了
Oh, I already found a guy online who's willing to sell.
你怎么知道这不是动漫展警察
How do you know this isn't a sting operation
布下的钓鱼计划呢
set up by the Comic-Con police?
就跟我知道
The same way I know
电视机里的人看不到我一样
that the people in the TV set can't see me.
谢尔顿  你随大流嘛
Sheldon, just come with us.
你怎么自己搞一个动漫展啊
You're not gonna make your own convention.
你们知道曾几何时
You know, there was a time
在世上还没有动漫展之前
when Comic-Con didn't exist at all
也是一位有理想的孤独梦想家打造起来的
until one lone dreamer with a unique vision made it happen.
你们听好了
And you mark my words--
我就是要去山寨他
I'm gonna rip that guy off.
是的  我要自己打造一个动漫展
Yes, I'm starting my own comic book convention,
我觉得你的客户  小罗伯特·唐尼[钢铁侠]
and I thought that your client, Robert Downey Jr.,
会是我们第一个访谈节目的完美出席嘉宾
would be perfect to appear on our first panel.
为什么你现在就拒绝了呢
Oh, well, now, why are you saying "no"?
你都还没问过他本人意见呢
You haven't even asked him yet.
不好意思啊
You know, excuse me,
但我当年耐着性子看完了《钢铁侠2》
but I sat through Iron Man 2.
他该抽出两个小时的时间  就当还给我
I believe he owes me two hours of his time.
他们居然挂我电话
They hung up on me.
你没有告诉他们  你的动漫展
Did you tell them that you're holding your convention
是在老牌连锁餐厅举办
at a Marie Callender's,
每一个受邀嘉宾能获得一块免费的派饼
and that every panelist gets a free slice of pie?
我都还没来得及说呢
I didn't even get to that part.
就连你的朋友威尔·惠顿都觉得
Look, even your friend Wil Wheaton thinks
这是在浪费时间
this is a waste of time.
才不是呢
Not true.
威尔觉得这是个很棒的主意
Wil thinks this is a great idea.
他只是担心
He was just concerned that
自己的名气不够大
he wasn't a big enough celebrity
无法担任如此重大活动的主打来宾
to headline such an amazing event.
而且那天他要洗胡子  抽不开身
Also, that's the same day that he shampoos his beard.
谢尔顿  兄弟  我真心觉得
Sheldon, buddy, I just don't think
你名单上的人是请不到的
this is going to come together for you.
你懂个屁
You don't know that.
这名单上还有几个一定会来的人
I still have plenty of solid leads on this list.
-那祝你好运  -先别走
- Good luck. - No, wait.
我要你帮我打电话给斯坦·李  伦纳德·尼莫伊
I need you to call Stan Lee, Leonard Nimoy
还有《比尔教科学》节目的比尔
and Bill Nye the Science Guy...
因为从法律上来说  我是禁止接触他们的
'cause, legally, I'm not allowed to.
对了  还有凯莉·费雪
Oh, and, also, Carrie Fisher,
《星球大战》中饰演莱娅公主的女星
后来沉迷毒品和酒精  还一度患上躁郁症
因为我听说她是个疯婆子
you know, 'cause I hear she can be pretty nuts.
我真不敢相信莱纳德
I can't believe Leonard is
居然花好几百块去买一张黄牛票
spending hundreds of dollars on scalped tickets.
上周  你也花这么多钱去买一条小裙子啊
Last week, you spent that on a little dress.
但黄牛票只能让动漫展为他敞开大门
Yeah, but those tickets only get him into Comic-Con.
而那裙子能让任何地方为我敞开大门
That dress gets me into anywhere I want.
那些黄牛票的确很贵
Those tickets were pretty expensive.
我只好让华仔预支他的零用钱
I had to give Howie an advance on his allowance.
这下他一定舍不得放开在动漫展买的玩具
Now he's never gonna put his toys away.
为什么他们不能像谢尔顿一样明智
Why can't they do something sensible like Sheldon
举办自己的动漫展呢
and start their own comic book convention?
好吧  谁想把我扔出去窗外
Also, who wants to throw me out that window?
当他们表现得像个小屁孩时
Oh, while they're acting like teenagers,
我们应该做点大人做的事
we could do something grown-up.
你是说去博物馆吗
Oh. You mean like a museum?
对  就像去博物馆那种  但不是
Yes, like a museum, but anything else.
我知道这附近有一个不错的酒店
Oh, I know. There's a nice hotel not far from here
那里可以喝下午茶
where they do afternoon tea.
下午茶  好高端洋气上档次啊
Ooh, afternoon tea-- how sophisticated of us.
好吧  如果我们要去高档场所
Oh, all right, if we're gonna be fancy,
那我最好穿上干净的内衣裤
I should probably put on clean underwear.
哎哟哟
La-dee-da!
某人居然还有干净的内衣裤
Look who has clean underwear.
我没有  所以路上得去超市一趟
No, we're gonna stop at Target on the way.
既然谢尔顿不去参加动漫展
Hey, since Sheldon's not going to Comic-Con,
或许我们可以打扮成帅酷三侠
maybe we could find a cool trio to dress up as.
不如我们打扮成神奇四侠
What if we go as The Fantastic Four,
就告诉其他人其实隐形女侠
and just tell people that the Invisible Girl
就站在咱们旁边
is standing there with us.
我还以为我们假装跟
Oh, and I thought our days of pretending
不存在的女人在一起的日子已经远去
to be with women who don't exist were over.
各位  我离为我的动漫展
Gentlemen, I am one step away
搞到一位重量级来宾  只有一步之遥啦
from securing a huge guest for my convention.
那一步是要用麻醉药把人迷晕
Does that step include chloroform
外加五花大绑吗
and a roll of duct tape?
我觉得对于詹姆斯·厄尔·琼斯来说
I don't think that will be necessary
完全不需要这样
for Mr. James Earl Jones.
你们听到了吧
You heard me.
他是《星际大战》中黑武士
The voice of Darth Vader,
和《狮子王》中父王的配音员
the Lion King's dad,
那句"这里是美国有线电视新闻网"也是他说的
and FYI, the guy who says, "This is CNN."
当然那声音听起来就像黑武士
Which also sounds like Darth Vader.
你怎么能请到詹姆斯·厄尔·琼斯
How are you gonna get James Earl Jones?
很简单  今天早些时候  他在微博上写
Simple. Earlier today, he Tweeted
他很期待晚上要去
that he's looking forward to going to
他最爱的寿司店吃晚餐
his favorite sushi restaurant for dinner.
我搜到四年前采访他的报道
I Googled an interview from four years ago
恰好是在他最爱的寿司店拍摄的
which was conducted in his favorite sushi restaurant.
他要去那里  我也会去那里
That's where he'll be, and that's where I'm going,
-然后  -然后在那里  黑武士
- and... - And that's where Darth Vader's
会把酱油倒在你头上
gonna pour soy sauce on your head.
谢尔顿  你要不要一起买黄牛票我无所谓
Sheldon, I don't care if you get scalped tickets with us or not,
但拜托别像个变态一样跟踪那个可怜的老头
but please don't be creepy and go stalking this poor guy.
你会给自己惹麻烦的
You're gonna get in trouble.
你们才会给自己惹麻烦呢
You're the ones who are going to get in trouble.
你们居然从一个陌生人手里
You're buying non-transferable tickets.
买不可转让出售的门票
And from a stranger, no less.
如果被抓到  你们不但会被禁止参加动漫展
Not only can you get banned from Comic-Con,
你们还可能被控告轻微盗窃罪
if caught, you could be charged with petty theft.
当我去警告詹姆斯·厄尔·琼斯在微博
You think about that while I'm warning James Earl Jones
泄露自己行踪的危险性时  你们好好反省下
about the danger of posting his location on Twitter.
这次碰到我是他走运
He got lucky this time.
现在外面很多怪胎跟踪狂呢
There are some weirdoes out there.
忘了拿钥匙了
Forgot my keys.
好的  可以  再见
Okay, great. Bye.
我们友好的黄牛党朋友说
Our friendly neighborhood scalper
他要晚点到
says he's running late.
他声音听起来像是罪犯吗
Does he sound like a criminal?
这话什么意思
What do you mean?
他会不会这么说话
You know, did he say things like,
"你们仨小弱鸡"  或者"你们给老子听好了"
"Youse guys," or "listen here, see?"
对  他迟到是因为
Yes. He-He's late
他得从1940年穿越过来
because he's on his way here from 1940.
提个醒嘛
I'm just saying.
我们不知道这家伙的底细
We don't know who this guy is.
要是他想偷我们的钱  想割我们的肾
What if he wants to steal our money or our kidneys,
或者是想剥我们的皮做衣服怎么办
or make a suit out of our skins?
人家干嘛要用你的皮肤做衣服啊
Why would someone want to make clothes out of your skin?
谁知道呢
I don't know.
没准是因为深色皮肤比较耐脏
Maybe 'cause dark doesn't show the stains?
你这么一说  我的确觉得
Well, now you're making me wonder
也许我们该选一个中立的地方见面
if we should have met him at a neutral location.
所以我才叫他到你家来啊
Why do you think I told him to come to your place?
这里的小孩子可真多
There sure are a lot of little kids here.
不敢相信我们居然以为这里会有成熟的感觉
I can't believe we thought this would makes us feel grown up.
我才不敢相信服务生以为我是你女儿
I can't believe the waiter thought I was your daughter.
我上一次梳妆打扮
Well, last time I got dressed up
享受下午茶时光还是在我五岁那年
and had tea was when I was five.
当时有我  我的泰迪熊  破烂娃娃和我的仓鼠
Just me, my teddy bear, Raggedy Ann and my hamster.
-好有爱啊  -的确如此
- That's cute. - It was.
直到我的仓鼠吃光了她的宝宝
Till my hamster ate all her babies.
立刻就不那么可爱了
It got less cute really fast.
我们走吗
Should we leave?
大厅那里有个酒吧
Well, there's a bar in the lobby.
我可以喝上一杯
I could go for a drink.
下午就开始喝酒  有其母必有其女
Drinking in the afternoon, just like her mommy.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
你一定喜欢《星际大战》吧
You like Star Wars.
要知道  我也演过其他电影
You know, I've been in other movies.
但对你来说其他电影根本无所谓  对吗
But you don't care about those, do you?
对你这种人  我只能说一句话
I have one thing to say to people like you...
我也好喜欢《星际大战》
I like Star Wars too.
愿意赏光坐下吗
Care to join me?
太谢谢你了
Thank you.
我的朋友莱纳德说
My friend Leonard said
要是在你吃饭时骚扰你
if I bothered you while you were eating,
你肯定以为我是个变态跟踪狂
you'd think I was a creepy stalker.
这位莱纳德听起来是个孬种呢
Well your friend Leonard sounds like a real weenie.
你说对了  厄尔·琼斯先生  他就是
He is, Mr. Earl Jones, he is.
我正在浏览一个动漫展的留言板
Okay, so, I'm on a Comic-Con message board,
有个家伙发了帖
and there's a post from a guy
说他冒用别人的票被发现了
where he says he got caught using someone else's badge...
而且谢尔顿也说对了
and Sheldon was right--
他被以轻微盗窃罪起诉了  各位
he did get charged with petty theft. Guys...
要是我穿着霹雳侠的服装被送进监狱
if I go to jail dressed as the Human Torch,
肯定会引起误会的
that might send the wrong message.
或许这的确不是个好主意
Maybe this isn't a good idea.
我可以给他发短信说我们反悔了
I can text the guy and tell him we changed our minds.
就这么做吧
Do it.
好呀
Okay.
我们正式决定不去动漫展
We're officially not going to Comic-Con.
等一下  我们总做同样的事
Hold on. We always do this.
-做什么事  -临阵退缩
- Do what? - Chicken out.
我们太害怕惹祸上身
We're-we're so afraid of getting into trouble
所以我们从来也不敢做坏事
that we never do anything wrong.
因为我们是好人啊
That's 'cause we're the good guys.
就算是蝙蝠侠也有不守规矩的时候
Even Batman breaks the rules.
你知道我对蝙蝠侠爱恨交加
You know I struggle with Batman.
就这一次也好
I-I say, this one time,
别再畏手畏脚了  让我们放纵一次吧
instead of wimping out, let's be badasses!
好呀  变坏就变坏
Okay, I'll be a badass--
可你要和人家打勾勾约定你也要变坏
but only if you pinky-swear to be one, too.
-霍华德  你要加入吗  -不用了
- Howard, you in on this? - No need.
哥就是一个不守规矩的活教材
I'm breaking rules all the time.
-举个例子  -昨晚
- Name one. - Last night.
我直接从瓶嘴喝了舒胃灵
Drank my Pepto straight out of the bottle.
你没用人家发附赠的小杯杯吗
What about that little cup they give you?
没错
Yeah.
那又怎么样
What about it?
有被他的气势震住吗
A-Are you impressed by that?
-有一点  -我也是
- A little. - Yeah, me, too.
当我读《帝国反击战》的剧本
You know, when I first read the script for Empire Strikes Back
第一次读到黑武士告诉卢克自己是他父亲时
and Darth Vader told Luke he was his father...
我想这家伙肯定在说谎
...I thought for sure he was lying.
我也有同感
Me, too!
可他没有说谎  对不对
But he wasn't, was he?
他没有
He was not!
还能再狗血一点吗
How messed up was that?!
太狗血了
So messed up.
我们一起去开心一下  好不好
What do you say let's go have some fun?
我老婆在纽约
My wife's in New York,
我有一张《狮子王》的酬金支票
and I got a Lion King residual check
都快在我口袋里磨出茧来了
burning a hole in my pocket.
所以  下午茶一点不好玩
So, afternoon tea was a bust.
从好的方面看  每个六岁的小女孩
On the bright side, every six-year-old there
都对我的皇冠羡慕嫉妒恨
was jealous of my tiara.
实话实说  这种感觉倍儿爽
Not gonna lie-- it felt good.
我问你
Let me ask you a question:
你们何时开始意识到自己长大成人了
When did you guys start feeling grown up?
因为我对自己有点迷惘了
'Cause I am not sure I do.
老实说  我以为结婚会让我变得成熟
Honestly, I thought when I got married I would,
可我依然觉得自己还在拼命装大人
but I still kind of feel like I'm pretending.
衣服都是童装部买的  难怪会底气不足
It doesn't help that most of my clothes come from Gap Kids.
我算是个成年人了
Okay, so I'm an adult,
那天我看到一位老人滑倒在地
and the other day I saw an old man slip and fall down,
于是我笑了
and I laughed.
笑得花枝乱颤
I mean, I laughed hard.
简直是  放声大笑
Like-like, out loud.
他如果没昏过去  肯定听到我在大声笑
If he was conscious, he would've heard me.
-天啊  -我知道
- Oh, my gosh. - I know.
他的助行器上垫底的网球掉了一颗
One of the tennis balls came off his walker
正好弹在他的头上  那真是
and bounced right off his head. I mean...
我差点笑尿了
I... I almost wet myself.
不身临其境是无法体会滴
I guess you had to be there.
我觉得我比你们都惨
I think I have you both beat.
试想一下  我得硬装出成熟
Imagine trying to feel like a grown-up
可我从来没跟男人发生过关系
when you've never even been with a man.
做爱不代表你就长大了
Okay, sex is not what makes you a grown-up.
对啊  不然这里你最老了
Yeah. Or you'd be the oldest one here.
是吗
Really?
你就这么跟你老妈说话的吗
Is that how you talk to your mother?
他停车了  马上上来
He just parked. He's on his way up.
太好了  好激动啊
Good. This is exciting.
-就是  -是啊
- It is. I feel alive. - Yeah.
就算我们被抓了又有什么所谓
What if we do get caught; who cares?
不就是被禁止参加动漫展嘛
So we get banned from Comic-Con.
-也许交个罚款  -不不
- Maybe slapped with a fine. - Oh, no.
我既是宇航员  又是坏男人
I'll be an astronaut and a bad boy--
女人怎么克制得住对我的冲动呢
how will women keep their pants on?
或许当我申请公民资格时  还能显摆一下这事
Uh, maybe it'll come up when I apply for citizenship.
靠  万一申请公民资格时  这事被知道了怎么办
Oh, crap, what if it comes up when I apply for citizenship?
不知道我们申请津贴时  这种事
I wonder if we'd have to disclose something like this
需不需要坦白上报
when we apply for grants.
他马上就来了  我们怎么办
He's gonna be here any second-- what should we do?
你们这两个没用的小屁孩
You guys are such babies.
交给哥处理吧
I'll handle this.
如果他以为我们不在家  就会走了
If he thinks we're not home, he'll go away.
你不是坏男人吗
I thought you were a badass.
舒胃灵的事我说谎了  我都是用小杯子喝的
I lied about the Pepto-- I always use the little cup!
你小时候  曾经是个结巴
Is it true, as a child, you were a stutterer
而且八年不能说话  这事是真的吗
and were functionally mute for eight years?
是真的
It is true.
他们用水中呼吸器制造出
Is it true they used scuba gear
黑武士的呼吸声  这事是真的吗
to create the sound of Darth Vader breathing?
是真的
They sure did.
你读过医学预科  差点成为医生
Is it true that you were premed in college
这事是真的吗
and you almost became a doctor?
千真万确
That's right.
詹姆斯
Oh, James!
你的故事  我听一整晚都不腻
I could listen to your stories all night.
说真的  长大成人有什么好的呀
I mean, really, what's so great about being grown up?
首先  这张账单可以三人平分
Well, for starters, we'd be splitting this check three ways.
我说真的  谁愿意做这些事啊
I'm serious. Who wants to do all that stuff?
买保险  还贷款
Have insurance, pay mortgages,
撞到停着的车后  还要留张自己联系方式的小条
leave one of those little notes when you hit a parked car.
我跟你说了是佩妮
I told you it was Penny.
拜托  不是我
Oh, come on, it wasn't me.
任何人都有可能撞掉你的后视镜
Anyone could have knocked your mirror off...
或是其它什么的
or whatever happened.
也许男生们说得对
Maybe the guys are right.
我们整晚都想显得成熟
I mean, we spent the whole night trying to be mature,
其实蛮无聊的
and it was kind of boring.
我相信他们一定比我们要玩得开心
I'm sure they're having more fun than we are.
老天爷  我现在
Oh, God, I could really use
还真用得着两大勺舒胃灵
exactly two tablespoons of Pepto right now.
洛杉矶
Hey, Los Angeles!
我和黑武士一起坐摩天轮
I'm on a Ferris wheel with Darth Vader!
他比你们想象的要友善多了
And he's nicer than you think!
是啊
I am!
* 在丛林里  非凡的丛林里 *
* In the jungle, the mighty jungle *
*  狮子今晚睡着了  *
* The lion sleeps tonight *
露一手  穆法沙
Bring it home, Mufasa.
《狮子今晚睡着了》是《狮子王》电影著名插曲
穆法沙是狮子王的父亲
我不明白这是做什么
I don't understand what we're doing.
这是谁的家
Whose house is that?
凯莉·费雪
Carrie Fisher.
她是个疯婆子
And she's a little crazy,
准备好闪人
so get ready to run.
这一点都不好玩  詹姆斯
It's not funny anymore, James!
那我为什么在笑呢
Then why am I laughing!
谢尔顿  这是完美之夜的
Ah, Sheldon, this is the perfect end
完美结局
to a perfect night.
好吧
Okay.
但我觉得卡拉OK时就已经是完美的结局
Yeah, but I think it could have ended with the karaoke.
你在脱衣舞俱乐部时想问我什么来着
What were you trying to ask me at the strip club?
让她们从我大腿上下去要花多少钱
How much does it cost to get them off my lap?
不  什么展的事
No. Something about a convention.
对哦  是这样的
Oh, right! Well...
我和小伙伴们今年没买到动漫展的票
my friends and I couldn't get into Comic-Con this year,
我想自己举办一个动漫展
and I was trying to start my own convention,
我想问你
and I was going to ask
你能受邀来参加访谈吗
if you would be a panelist.
你和小伙伴们何不跟我一起去动漫大会呢
Why don't you and your friends come to Comic-Con with me?
-真的吗  -当然
- Really? - Of course.
而且地球上我最爱的城市
And San Diego is right across the border
就在圣地亚哥边界旁
from my favorite city on Earth,
提华纳[墨西哥城市  毒品猖獗]
Tijuana...
我每晚都会带你去
...where I'm taking you every night!
亲娘滴
Ay-yi-yi.
亲娘滴  好爽哦
Ay-yi-yi, bang-bang.
博·布里奇斯在我肩膀上
So, Beau Bridges is on my shoulders,
杰夫·布里奇斯在马龙·白兰度的肩膀上
and Jeff Bridges is on Marlon Brando's shoulders,
别忘了  我们没得到进泳池的允许
and remember, we do not have permission to be in the pool--
谢尔顿  醒醒
Hey! Sheldon, wake up!
然后
And...
安吉·迪金森准备放狗咬我们
Angie Dickinson is about to sic the dogs on us,
我跳下水  马龙也跳下水
and I go under the water and Marlon goes under the water,
水花溅起了两尺高
and the water raises about two feet
溅得她露台上到处都是
and sloshes all over her patio,
把狗吓坏了  拼命逃跑
and the dogs freak out and run like hell,
然后我们也拼命逃跑
and then we run like hell...
老天啊
Oh, boy!
太搞笑了
That was a lot of fun.
安吉·迪金森是谁啊
Uh... who's Angie Dickinson?